Thank you for watching
ME
Akimoto Nakasetara Software
me
Akimoto, who has seen off the graduation of all the members up to now, is now at the peak of her tearfulness, even though it is her own graduation.
So the junior members challenged Akimoto to make her cry by any means necessary. If Akimoto could make her cry within the time limit, the junior members would get a reward.
However, Akimoto knew about the plan, and he secured the reward if the junior members shed tears.
Senpai vs. juniors' crying bauble This time, we started with a match against Mukai.
I'm going to try my best to move Manatsu-san with my special skill.
Trying to make her cry with frogs and stuff
What's your strategy for using Mukai's special skill?
Good morning, Manatsu-san. Sorry for starting this morning.
I'm holding a guitar.
To show my appreciation to you, Manatsu-san.
I thought I'd sing a little song.
Do you have any requests?
Are you okay with this?
Do you like "Kikkou"?
I like it, teacher... please tell me
Tell me you like me at 4:00 and 6:00.
It's not a trigger.
It's not... not a trigger.
Pinch.
I've done this a lot.
How many are there now?
When I first came on Makiizaka Kenkenchu.
I did a story about serving midsummer fruits in a bowl of tendon.
I remember that.
When I saw your face, I wanted to pull it out.
I'm sorry.
You're laughing once.
It's good.
It's nice.
I was really nervous for my first time on the set of "Construction Work".
I didn't want to bother my senpai.
I was trying not to bother my seniors.
Manatsu-san took a picture with everyone.
I felt like I was accepted.
I remember I was so happy.
You're definitely full of energy, aren't you?
I remember it so well.
MukaiRemembering her debut, she was so energetic that tears dropped.
Akimoto: You didn't do anything, but you got another reward.
I didn't do anything.
I kind of messed up at first.
You're going to pull it?
I'd like to pull it properly from here.
Thank you.
I'll play the song you said you liked, Manatsu-san.
I'll play it for you.
From Eifukucho Station, cross the street.
Walk along the side of Taisho-kata.
Turn at the crossroads and go down the hill
I can see your house and your memories
I heard the sound of wind chimes somewhere
Summer was doing its thing
Hang in there
Why did I come all the way here alone?
I'll never see you again
my feet swell without knowing it
Even now, whenever I feel sad
I think of your kind face
I'm getting back on my feet
They shed tears, but here Akimoto lost more tears and
I wish we could spend time together.
I wish I could tell you how grateful I am for everything you've done for me.
And first laughter, first half laughter, second half tears, that's already Masayuki Sada's way, isn't it?
Really, really.
That's the best way to do it.
It's the best way.
They had already shed tears, but now Akimoto lost more tears and said, "I want to spend time together with you.
I wanted to spend time with you both.
I wanted to spend time with you. I wanted to thank you for everything you've done for me.
And it's Masayuki Sada's way of laughing at first and crying in the second half.
It's true, it's true.
They both burst into tears, but then Akimoto lost more tears and said, "I want to spend time with you.
I wanted to spend time with you both.
I wanted to spend time with you. I wanted to express my gratitude for what you have done for me.
And it's Masayuki Sada's way to start off with laughter and end with tears.
I didn't do anything, so it's not much.
He brought it to Azuki.
Sorry, it's a bit crumpled.
I'm so happy.
Thank you very much.
I'm so glad. It's like a reverse surprise.
Yes, it is.
Didn't you ever wonder who signed Akimoto's guitar?
I've always wondered about that.
I did think about that.
It's Nankoyuki.
That's amazing.
Is it signed by Nankosetsu?
I had a chance to sing with him before, so I got it there.
That's amazing.
And for someone who has known you since Akimoto, you only put it on that tape.
It's strange that you prepared so much.
Azuki was the one who prepared it.
What was that written?
It was a message to Azuki.
What?
Is it different?Has it changed?
I wondered what you were doing now.
I thought, "Wow, I got my nouveau bra out.
What do you mean?
Mukai?
What? Can I ask what it said?
That's a secret, isn't it?
Just tell me the first thing.
To Azuki.
That part's true.
How did you end it?
Manatsu.
I don't know.
I understand that.
Challenger Akimoto.
Both of them broke the all-time Nakase record.
The next Nakase person will be Summer.
I thought, "I don't have many chances to talk with Ms. Manatsu anymore.
So, I drew a picture of Manatsu-san.
Well, you know...
It's not a making of.
The painter showed a video of the making of the illustration, which is his specialty, and tried to draw tears.
Oh, I was so surprised.
The kind that makes you cry.
I really like the hug between Ikuta-san and Manatsu-san in this song.
What's this? I'm so happy.
Surprise.
It's amazing. This is how you drew it.
That's right.
It's amazing. Really.
Wow.
Mochi.
The artist chose the outfit from Uniform Mannequin, Akimoto's debut single.
She's welcoming me right away.
I've been thinking of writing it and giving it to her someday.
I'm so happy. Because you gave it to me on my birthday.
And your birthday.
I'm buying a frame of this size right now to put next to the review.
Really?
Because I look at it every day.
I'm happy.
Did you cry?
The one and only illustration in the world that he put his heart and soul into dropped Akimoto's tears!
Akimoto, who had been on the defensive, began to fight back from here!
I was worried about the people around me even more than that, because I was the center of the group, and I should really be the star of the show, but I was worried about the people around me.
I was worried about some things, but thanks to Kakki's support, we were able to get through the whole summer tour, so I really don't mean to flatter you.
And that's the end of the tour where Akimoto made us cry in reverse!
It's so early, isn't it, everyone's already crying within a minute or two?
The fact that they were planning to make her cry means that they knew she was going to do it, and they cried.
Also, after the VTR started, Mr. Himura's chair wouldn't get down.
I'm already thinking about that today.
This is...
I don't know why.
That's why I've been doing something like this.
I've been doing this.
I thought it was a little high when I saw it today when they started saying "Dawn".
I was really high when Dawn started, and I was like...
I thought I should do something to match.
I thought that's why you got fat here.
It's not my fault.
New ones are here.
You have a new one? Amazing.
Two of each.
Which one do you have?
This one's mine, this one's mine.
This one, this one.
I don't really care about this scene.
It would be funny if you cried in the space between the chairs right now.
It would be funny if you cried.
This kind of interaction could suck.
Oh, no, it's nothing.
Don't cry with your eyes like this.
Cry, I want it to be outrageous.
I want you to rest now.
I want you to be the best, I want you to be the best, I want you to be the best, I want you to be the best, I want you to be the best, I wonder who it is
Captain vs. vice-captain Nakase Battlespur I have a lot to talk to you about.
I've got a lot to tell you... but since we're here, I thought we'd make up a theme and have a little chat.
The presenter brought a card with a homemade theme on it, and the content of the talk that he turned up was to make the audience cry.
I don't know.
Do you remember when we first met?
That Nogichu? Yes, that's right. He was just like he was on TV... soft and gentle.
He was so soft. From there, we got closer and closer.
He even started to show us his clumsy side and his crying side.
She even started to show me her crying.
They're reminiscing and smiling... I wonder if there will be no more tears...
I'm getting to know her more and more, and now I really love her as a person.
And then...
Which one of you is this?
I'm crying my eyes out...
Remembering the time when we met, Umezawa's "collapse switch" was turned on.
Akimoto, who's a fast woman and has no middle finger, got caught up in the crying and went on to say "fastest time, fastest time!
I don't know...
I got to know many things about Manatsu-san... and those things...
As I got to know more and more about her, the more I realized that the way she showed her performance as the captain was...
I think she's working really hard.
You're so dependable, and I think only you can do that.
I think she's the one who wants to be pampered.
Even when you're the one who stands out...
Even when you stand out... she'll always bring someone forward.
If I asked you if you're being selfish...I asked Manatsu-san if he was being selfish.
She suddenly burst into tears.
Manatsu-san cried.
I thought she was holding back.
I really remember that.
I really want you to think only of yourself, but you would never do that, Manatsu san.
You put the members first.
Please be selfish.
Akimoto, whose lucency has been loosened, cried a lot during this talk.
And the exclusive talk between the captain and vice-captain never stops.
I have so many memories with Ume.
Even before I became vice-captain, she knew me as vice-captain.
I don't really have anything to say to Ume.
And lately...
Ume used to only show her strong side.
But when I see you goofing around and showing your weaknesses to your juniors, I feel so relieved.
It makes me want to see Nogizaka with Ume at the top.
I love your Nogizaka. I love it!
I love you too!
I'll protect you. Please show me.
I'll be watching you closely! They exchanged passionate shouts of encouragement, which you wouldn't expect from a variety show.
Time was up with both of them in tears!
The score was not handled at all... but the one that was buried pretty well... this conversation between the captains was very hot.
That was really bad, and I cried so hard afterwards that I cried thinking about it.
The version and the various lines lasted one minute, and the studio screamed.
The last challenge was by Tsutsui.
I'm probably going in a slightly different direction than everyone else, but I'm confident that I'll give it my all and make her cry.
I'm going to give it my all and make you cry.
What?
Good morning.
Manatsu-san...
Huh?
Please sit here
What's with this room?
Huh?
What's this?
Well, this time...
I'm here with Ms. Manatsu, who's graduating.
Midsummer and stairs in the middle of winter.
I wanted to enjoy my favorite staircase together.
I asked her to make a tea house for us.
This is crying.
You mean make me cry with fear!
I heard this story from a friend of mine.
There was a 20-year-old college student.
There was a guy named Takashi.
He had a girlfriend named Mafuyu.
One night
Takashi was living alone in his apartment
Takashi was home alone.
What?
You really called?
Really.
It was Midsummer calling.
Can I go to Takashi's now?
He said he'd be there in half an hour.
So Takashi waited at home.
But 30 minutes passed, and Mafuyu still hadn't arrived.
I wonder what's wrong.
Maybe the train is late.
I wondered...
Wow! What a surprise! What is it?
I heard a pounding on the front door.
What's that? I wondered why the intercom wasn't ringing.
I wondered if the intercom was broken.
I was about to go to the front door.
Oh, what a surprise!
I got another call.
What's wrong? Midwinter. I said I'd open the front door now.
Don't open the door!
A woman on all fours, dressed all in black, just now climbed up on the front porch.
She was banging on the Takashin's door.
What?
She climbed up on the roof and went to the balcony.
Takashi?
What?
I thought, "What?
And when he looked back at the window, there it was!
Wow! That's scary.
Scary! Ow! Ow!
Ow!
Whoa! Okay, okay!
Whoa!
No, rap, rap.
Hey, no, no, wait, no! No! No! No! No! A little more!
What? Watch out! Look out!
What the hell?
I'm scared.
That's all. I thought it was over.
I'm too scared. What? Neither of you are crying.
What's wrong? Are you scared all of a sudden?
Tears in my eyes, but they haven't fallen yet.
Now, the last plan! Still no plan?
I brought a present for Manassa at the end. A present?
I'm scared of presents with this tone.
I thought it would be perfect for Manassa, so I asked her to open it.
Hanya.
My father's graduation present was a mannequin head for haircuts.
What are you doing?
Wow! You scared me!Wow! You scared me!
Isn't she scary as hell?
Was she like that?
Oh, my God!
Akimoto manages to keep her tears from spilling, and is attacked by her horror father!
And here comes the counterattack!
I heard that Ayume might meet you today.
I brought something for you, too.
It's in here.
We did a tour in the summer, and it's been three years since you've been on the road.
Akimoto wants to make you cry no matter what it takes.
Akimoto, who wanted to cry no matter what, completed the gold tape message operation he used to welcome us here again.
He's always there to support the group, and I can always feel it.
I can always feel it.
I'm sure you have a lot of thoughts and difficulties, but you don't say them to others.
But you don't talk about it to others.
You're the youngest member of the group.
I think it's cool that you have such strength.
I really respect you as a person.
Are you okay?
I want you to keep it.
Akimoto, you got them all.
Thank you.
I'll put my power in it.
Thank you very much.
Only Tsutsui failed.
Tsutsui's horror plan failed and too many tears flowed
Akimoto's golden tape freedom ceremony brought tears to my eyes.
She made everyone cry.
Why are you trying to make us cry with that?
I wanted to go in a different direction from everyone else
I thought everyone would come from different directions.
I thought everyone was coming from different directions, but it was just the emotional ones.
It's like I'm the weird one.
When that scary story starts, I just keep laughing.
I know what I'm talking about, so I'm laughing... more and more.
I thought they were trying to make me cry.
It's funny all the time.
That paper.
I'm sorry to all the people I gave it to.
I gave it to someone else.
I gave one to Ume too.
But it seemed like I wasn't the only one who got it.
I got the feeling that you just found out about it.
I was just watching the video, thinking what if it's the same sentence now?
You were just wrong.
It wasn't.
It didn't sound canned.
That's a good point.
It wasn't canned.
And to Akimoto and the member who made him cry, a reward for this project.
When I said we talked about canulés.
Patisserie Parola!
Cannoulet.
They're so good!
Your reward is a canulé made with French fermented butter, which Bananaman recommended earlier.
Patisserie Parola's canele!
After making 8 people cry, Akimoto got 8 canulés!
They are so good!
350 yen per piece!
High quality!
After making Akimoto cry, he tried to eat the canele!
They are so delicious!
It's so good, I can't stop staring at it!
I'm just staring at it
This is so good!
It's so good, isn't it?
It's my favorite type of canele!
I'm so grateful. Let me try a little something.
It's so good!
I'm sorry about the planning of this event, but Akimoto knew about it, too.
It was a surprise in reverse, but from this point on, even Akimoto didn't know about it.
What?
I received a letter.
Who is it?
I'd like to read it for you.
Yes, sir.
Go for it, eh?
Congratulations on your graduation. At first, I was worried about entering this world and was against it, but now...
I've been so happy to be a part of this wonderful group called Nogizaka46. I've decided for years that my last summer tour would be a nationwide tour, so last year's tour was a great opportunity for me to go all over the country with my dad.
You went all over the country with my dad. When I saw fans, I thanked them from the bottom of my heart.
You have a long life ahead of you after you graduate from Nogizaka46. Nacchan is a girl who has her own ideas, so please believe in yourself and keep going.
I'll protect you no matter what happens, and I know I'm not always there to help you, but you can tell me anything. I'll talk to you a lot more from now on.
Here's a cannulator for you, Mommy.
Thank you, Mom. What a surprise!
I was really surprised.
It's going to be like it's the last one today.
There's still a few more shows to go.
What's with all the crying?
Nobuseta46's 32nd single will be released on March 22nd!
And the selected members for the 32nd single will be announced at the next Buseta Kensetsu Chu!
Tickets for the Birthday Live are now on sale!
Nogizaka Soul Master Opening
Yes!
Special Yomiuri Hint: Member Minister Election
It's a quick fix!
Who will be number one?
9:00 p.m. draw.
What's with the funny face?
Please subscribe to our channel!Please subscribe to our channel!